

# KELVIN LEUNG

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

# **ABOUT ME**

A positive and self-motivated full-stack developer with 8+ years of commercial experience in several different front-end and back-end languages, database, responsive frameworks, mobile app development with Java for Android devices & Swift for iOS devices, and best code practices.

### CONTACT

### Address:

Brisbane, Australia

### **Email:**

kelvinleung.aus@gmail.com

#### Website:

http://kelvinleung.me

### LinkedIn:

https://linkedin.com/in/kelvinlwy

### GitHub:

https://github.com/kelvinlwy

# **SKILLS**

#### **Programming Languages:**

JS (+ES6) • Java • Swift • Objective-C • SQL

# **Mobile Development:**

Android • iOS (Swift)

### Web Technologies:

Node.js • CSS3 (+SASS) • HTML5 • Jquery • ReactJs (+Redux) • React Native • AngularJs

### Database:

 $\mathsf{MySQL} \bullet \mathsf{PostgreSQL} \bullet \mathsf{MongoDB}$ 

### Others:

AWS • Yarn • NPM • Git

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Co-Founder & Tech Lead

2017 - Present

### HAPPY DINOSAUR PTY LTD

Happy Dinosaur is an advertising startup which has established an innovative strategy to transform underutilised spaces, like takeaway coffee cups, table surfaces, and so forth to a medium and cafes to hubs for delivering business messages to local audiences.

My lead role is to design & develop both web (with React, Node.Js, HTML5, CSS3, AWS) & mobile (with React Native) marketplace for CMS and services through performing requirements analysis, design, technology sourcing to implementation, maintenance, and product analysis; manage digital marketing and social media advertising.

# Full Stack Developer (Contract Role)

Mar, 2017 - Sep, 2017

#### CHAPTECH

I am responsible for building a web platform to manage IoT devices and effectively visualise data to end users. Responsibilities:

- Develop a complex web application from scratch for both frontend (with HTML5, CSS3, ReactJs) and backend (with Hapi.js, Node.js, MySQL)
- Implement GIS by using Mapbox API
- API design and development
- Interface design, testing, debugging, maintenance, and application stability & performance improvement

# Android Lead & Web Developer

May 2016 - Mar, 2017

# IRECRUIT AUSTRALIA

I am responsible for the full life-cycle Android development through design, project architecture, implementation to debugging & troubleshooting, testing, and product release; the web application front-end development from project planning to translating UI design into code and handling & presenting business logic visually in the web interface.

# Software Developer

Jun 2011 - Apr, 2016

### **LOCATRIX COMMUNICATIONS**

- Professional Android development with Java & iOS development with Swift
- Involved in full life-cycle mobile app development for both enterprise internal & commercial products from the ground up to ready-to-go product
- Involved in few web application project for frontend development

**Key Projects**: • Bourne Movie Android App (NBC Universal)

• Game of Phones (Virgin Mobile Australia)

CS Coordinator
Air Export Ops Officer

VANTEC WORLD TRANSPORT(HK) LTD
UPS SUPPLY CHAIN SOLUTIONS

# **EDUCATION**

# **Griffith University**

### **BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING**

2008 - 2011

Bachelor of Engineering, Electronic & Computer Engineering with Class IIA Honours

# **REFERENCE**

# **ALEKSANDAR SVETSKI**

Former CEO, iRecruit Australia Phone: +61 417 165 003

# **MARK WHITE**

CEO, Locatrix Communications Phone: +61 438 900 880